## SATHISH KUMAR.C

Addess:

No.J205, J-Block,

TVS Greenhills Apartment,

Alapakkam, perungalathur, Chennai-63.

Email : <u>sathish.ece17@gmail.com</u>

Mobile : +91-8675454147,6380332986

## **OBJECTIVE:**

Looking forward to a challenging and competitive work atmosphere leading to a professional experience with a dynamic and progressive organization where my skills, talents and abilities will be utilized to the fullest for mutual benefit.

# **EXPERIENCE SUMMARY:**

### Totally 7 years of experience in General insurance and Banking Domain.

Skilled and meticulous Retention Specialist with an exceptional record of strong customer service. Able to handle a different vendors with top-notch courtesy and professionalism. Outstanding multitasker who thrives in a fast-paced high-pressure work environment.

## PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE:

# Kotak Mahindra Bank

Manager (auto loan) - May 2020 to till Date

Primary responsibilities include maintaining highly valued customers by utilizing key relationship building skills and effective customer service techniques. Handles all of the necessary transactions involved in selling both used and new cars to prospective customers

#### **RESPONSIBILITY:**

- Ensure high level employee execution of daily calls service levels by maximizing customer service opportunities
- Responsible for providing supportive and effective management to channel and Customer.
- Arranged financing and reviewed required documents to determine approval/rejection..
- Maintained positive relationships with channels.
- Strategically provided appropriate resolutions that were optimal solutions for a valued based customer.
- Handled escalated complex customer issues.
- Handled the branch customers and various portfolios customers like KPTR.
- Responsible to conduct Joint Calls daily with team which includes Source visits and Sales calls.
- Troubleshooting with :-
  - Underwriting team for policy approval
  - Service Centre operations team for policy issuance
  - Service Centre claims team for claims settlement
  - Finance team for timely disbursement of agent's commission

WIPRO INFOTECH – As Quality Analyst (April 2013 – Nov 2013).

ROYAL SUNDARAM GENERAL INSURANCE CO LTD (Nov 2013- july 2014).

BAJAJ ALLIANZ GENERAL INSURANCE CO LTD as a RRE(Oct 2014 – Mar 2016)

RELIANCE GENERAL INSURANCE CO LTD as a Associate Manager (March 2016 to Nov 2017)

HDFC BANK as Deputy Manager (April 2018 - Feb 2020)

#### **ACHIEVEMENTS:**

- Won "Best Performer" award twice within a year experience in HDFC bank.
- Brought the Chennai COP channel PAN India Top Position and maintained 1<sup>st</sup> position in HDFC bank.
- Received "Excellence award" for All time High auto loan business achievement in HDFC Bank.
- Won "Best performer" award with cash Reward for outstanding Contribution in ROYAL SUNDARAM.
- Received many appreciations from dealers and Customers for providing appropriate resolutions with the emphasis of Customer satisfaction in BAJAJ ALLIANZ.
- Have achieved bench mark retention ratio in RELIANCE GENERAL INSURANCE CO LTD.SSSS

# STRENGTH:

- Excellent leadership and Monitoring skills
- Strong problem solver
- Time Management.
- Motivator
- Trustworthy

#### **EDUCATION:**

B.E., Electronics and Communication, University: Anna university (2007-2011)

# **PERSONAL DETAILS:**

Father Name: Chandiran A

Blood group: A+ ve.

DOB: 24/05/1989. MARITAL STATUS: Married.

LANGUAGES KNOWN: Tamil, English.

#### **DECLARATION:**

I hereby declare that the above mentioned information is correct up to my knowledge and I bear the responsibility for the correctness of the above mentioned particulars.

Place: chennai

Date: (SATHISH KUMAR.C)